<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Fountain City Cycling</string>
    <string name="title_section4">Setting</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Notes</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Trips</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Record</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_input">Record</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_trip_purpose">Trip Purpose</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user_info">User Information</string>
    <string name="title_activity_trip_map">Trip Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_saved_trips">Saved Trips</string>
    <string name="title_activity_trip_detail">Trip Details</string>
    <string name="title_activity_note_type">Note Type</string>
    <string name="title_activity_note_detail">Note Details</string>
    <string name="title_activity_note_map">Note Map</string>
    <string name="title_activity_saved_notes">Saved Notes</string>

    <string-array name="ageArray">
        <item></item>
        <item>Less than 18</item>
        <item>18–24</item>
        <item>25–34</item>
        <item>35–44</item>
        <item>45–54</item>
        <item>55–64</item>
        <item>65+</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="genderArray">
        <item></item>
        <item>Female</item>
        <item>Male</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ethnicityArray">
        <item></item>
        <item>White</item>
        <item>African American</item>
        <item>Asian</item>
        <item>Native American</item>
        <item>Pacific Islander</item>
        <item>Multi-racial</item>
        <item>Hispanic / Mexican / Latino</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="incomeArray">
        <item></item>
        <item>Less than $20,000</item>
        <item>$20,000 to $39,999</item>
        <item>$40,000 to $59,999</item>
        <item>$60,000 to $74,999</item>
        <item>$75,000 to $99,999</item>
        <item>$100,000 or greater</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="cyclefreqArray">
        <item></item>
        <item>Less than once a month</item>
        <item>Several times a month</item>
        <item>Several times per week</item>
        <item>Daily</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="ridertypeArray">
        <item></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Strong & fearless]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[Enthused & confident]]></item>
        <item>Comfortable, but cautious</item>
        <item>Interested, but concerned</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="riderhistoryArray">
        <item></item>
        <item>Since childhood</item>
        <item>Several years</item>
        <item>One year or less</item>
        <item>Just trying it out / just started</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="email_hint">name@domain</string>
    <string name="zip_hint">12345</string>

    <string-array name="trippurposeArray">
        <item>Commute</item>
        <item>School</item>
        <item>Work-Related</item>
        <item>Exercise</item>
        <item>Social</item>
        <item>Shopping</item>
        <item>Errand</item>
        <item>Other</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="title_activity_main">Fountain City Cycling</string>

    <!--=============================================-->
    <!-- Instruction TextViews in activity_user_info -->
    <!--=============================================-->
    <string name="instruction_1">Upon launching the app, you\'ll find yourself on the <b>Record</b> screen.\n\n
        Confirm the iPhone has a good fix on your location by checking the map before tapping Start.
        (GPS conditions sometimes prevent accurate location. If this is the case, cycle a short distance
        and check again.)  \n\nWhen you\'re ready to start recording your ride, tap <b>Start.</b></string>
    <string name="instruction_2">When your ride is over, tap <b>Save.</b> Confirm that your trip is done by
        tapping <b>Save</b> in the next pop-up. If you don\'t want to save the trip and upload the data - for
        whatever reason - simply choose <b>Discard.</b> If you tap Save by accident and want to continue recording
        your current trip, choose <b>Continue</b>.\n\nIf you have switched to another app while recording
        your ride, you can get back to Fountain City Cycling by selecting it from your Home Screen or from
        the App Switcher. If your battery goes below a 20% charge, Fountain City Cycling will automatically stop
        recording and shut down.</string>
    <string name="instruction_3">Select a purpose on the <b>Trip Purpose</b> screen and tap <b>Save.</b> We\'re
        interested in the MAIN purpose for each trip you make. If you\'re unsure how to categorize a
        trip, select <b>Other</b> from the Trip Purpose chooser. You can always include a comment before
        transmitting.\n\nFountain City Cycling will prompt you to enter comments or notes on the ride, which you can
        skip if you have none. It will then upload your ride data, notifying you when done. If there\'s a problem
        connecting to the server, it will prompt you to retry at another time.</string>
    <string name="instruction_4">After your data is uploaded, Fountain City Cycling displays the map of your ride,
        showing the route, distance travelled, and average speed.\n\nTap <b>My Trips</b> on the tab-bar at the
        bottom of the screen to show a list of all your rides, including dates, times, mileage, CO2 saved,
        and calories burned. Tap on a trip to display its map. Share the map with others by taking a
        screenshot (press Sleep/wake and Home simultaneously), and sending it via email or downloading
        it to your computer. Hint: you can zoom in or out on the map. Tap <b>Edit</b> on the trip list to delete
        a trip.</string>
    <string name="instruction_5">Do you know of an asset that will help other cyclists along your route - such
        as good bike parking, a water fountain, or a secret passage to cut through? Or have you noticed an
        issue you\'d like to see addressed - such as a traffic signal that won\'t change or a problem with a
        bike lane? Tap on <b>Note this</b> and choose the issue or assets from the pop-up and then tap <b>Save</b>.
        \n\nIf none of the options fit your observation, choose <b>Note this asset</b> or <b>Note this issue</b>
        and you can fill in additional details on the next screen. Tap <b>Save</b> on the <b>Detail</b> screen to
        upload your issue or asset.</string>
    <string name="instruction_6">You can add an optional photo or additional details for each issue and asset,
        or skip either one and just tap <b>Save</b> to upload your note.\n\nTap <b>Add photo</b> to open the camera
        and take a photo of the issue or asset. You can then preview your photo, and either tap <b>Use</b>, or
        <b>Retake</b> if you want to take it again. Type any optional notes in the <b>Additional Details</b> box.</string>
    <string name="instruction_7">Tap <b>My Notes</b> on the tab-bar at the bottom of the screen to show a list of
        all your assets (in blue) and issues (in red), with dates and times.\n\nTap on a note to display
        its map. You can then tap the <b>i</b> for Info to see the picture and additional details, if any, that
        you entered for this note. Tap <b>Edit</b> on the top of the <b>My Notes</b> page to delete a note.</string>
    <string name="instruction_8">Entering personal info is completely optional and confidential, and, if you
        choose to participate, only has to be done once. It involves a few basic questions useful to our
        study. If you wish to give us your email address, the City of Columbus may contact
        you directly about your experience using Fountain City Cycling or bicycling in the city. Tap <b>Save</b> when
        finished.\n\nThis Help menu is available from <b>Getting started with Fountain City Cycling</b>.</string>
    <string name="steps_working_properly">For your own safety, please do not listen to music with your
        headphones, talk on the phone, or look at the screen while cycling. Please pull over before
        reporting an asset or issue on your trip.\n\nBe sure to enable Location in your phone\'s Settings.
        (From the Home page, go to Settings, then Location Services.)</string>

</resources>